http://www.newyankee.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Menu
MENUMENUHOMEABOUTSTORE
BedsBookcasesChestsCupboardsDesksGardenKids' StuffKitchenSeatingSpecialtyTablesWorkshop
WATCHFAQTHIS OLD HOUSE
THIS OLD HOUSE VENTURES, LLC
PRIVACY POLICY
THIS OLD HOUSE VENTURES, LLC and its subsidiary and affiliates (collectively, “TOHV”) respects the privacy rights of our users and is strongly committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to its Websites, magazine, any information collected and provided to TOHV when you subscribe digitally to thisoldhouse.com, House.one, Newyankee.com (“Website”) or the TOHV magazine and information collected offline when you subscribe to the print edition of the TOHV magazine, but does not apply to any other product or service of TOHV, unless otherwise expressly indicated by TOHV (such as by including a link to this Privacy Policy on other TOHV websites or on TOHV mobile applications).
Collection and Use of Your Personal Information
TOHV, or where relevant a designated service provider, collects personal information that you voluntarily provide on this Website, on third-party websites and applications when subscribing digitally to the Website or TOHV Magazine, or offline in connection with your TOHV Magazine print edition subscription, which may include your name, address, email address, contact information, credit card number, billing information, password etc. For example, TOHV or a designated service provider collects personal information when you register on this Website, request certain TOHV services or products, or submit the information to enter a sweepstakes, contest, or other promotion. If you do not provide certain personal information, not all functionality on the site will be available.
Do not provide information about others unless you are authorized to do so and consent to have all information used, disclosed, and transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By submitting the information about others, you represent and warrant that you are authorized to do so and that you have received authorization from the person about whom you are providing the information and that person has consented to have all information used, disclosed, and transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
We use this information for carefully considered business purposes which also benefit our customers, and which include some or all of the following:
• to provide our services and products
• to communicate with you
• to help TOHV improve our services and products and develop new services and products
• to provide support for our services and products, and for TOHV internal quality control purposes
• to provide you with offers and promotions about services and products of TOHV or of other parties that may be of interest to you
• to enhance your experience with this Website, including to save your preference and login information
• to analyze Website usage and analyze use of the Website
• to protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of TOHV or others and to monitor compliance with and enforce the terms of any agreement with TOHV
• to operate our services, products, and systems properly.
We use any credit card or payment information we acquire from you to fulfill your order. You may instruct TOHV at any time not to use your personal information covered by this Privacy Policy to provide you with offers and promotions by clicking here or, if you are TOHV Magazine subscriber, by clicking on the TOHV Magazine Opt-out form. You can also update your settings for receiving offers and promotions by clicking here. Please note that if you exercise choice in this manner, you will continue to receive communications concerning your account and products and services you requested, and in response to any requests for information by you. Please also note that this opt-out process may take some time to complete, consistent with applicable law.
TOHV or a designated service provider may takes photographs for security purposes which may available to TOHV users worldwide.
Use of Cookies And Other Electronic Tools
TOHV and the parties with whom we work (e.g., service providers, business partners, advertisers and advertising servers) may place, view, and/or use “cookies”, Web server logs, Web beacons, or other electronic tools to collect statistical and other information about your use of this Website and other websites. This information may include information about the IP address of your computer, browser type, language, operating system, your mobile device, device ID, geo-location data, the state or country from which you accessed this Website, the Web pages visited, the date and the time of a visit, the websites you visited immediately before and after visiting this Website, the number of links you click within this Website, the functions you use on this Website, the databases you view and the searches you request on this Website, the data you save on or download from this Website and the number of times you view an advertisement.
TOHV and the parties with whom we work may use the information collected for various reasons, either on behalf of TOHV or for the other parties’ own purposes, including research, analysis, to better serve visitors to this Website (such as by enabling log-in, providing access to certain sections of this Website, providing customized content, or presenting online advertising on this Website or other websites tailored to your interests as described further below), to compile aggregate and anonymous information about usage of this Website and other websites, other statistics, etc. However, if you have deleted and disabled cookies, these uses will not be possible to the extent they are based on cookie information. To opt out of google analytics tracking, including Demographics and Interest Reporting, please click here.
To assist us with the uses described in this Privacy Policy, information collected about your use of this Website or other websites may be aggregated, analyzed or combined with personal or other information about you from other online or offline sources. If you prefer that we not combine non-personal information that has been collected, through cookies, about your use of this Website or other websites with personal or other information about you, then please delete and disable cookies for each browser, on each computer you use to surf the Web.
Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to disable cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. Likewise, most mobile devices allow you to disable the ability for geo-location information to be collected from your mobile device. The help function on most browsers and mobile devices contains instructions on how to set your browser to notify you before accepting cookies, disable cookies entirely, or disable the collection of geo-location data. You need to set each browser, on each device you use to surf the Web. Thus, if you use multiple browsers (e.g., Chrome, Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.), you should repeat this procedure with each one. Similarly, if you connect to the Web from multiple devices (e.g., work and home), you need to set each browser on each device. Depending on your jurisdiction, you may be able to utilize additional cookie management tools. However, if you disable cookies or refuse to accept a request to place a cookie, it is possible that some parts of this Website, such as the polls, surveys, contests, and product sales, and certain areas of the Website for which you need to log in, will not function properly, and the advertising you receive when you visit this Website may not be advertisements tailored to your interests.
Advertisements
TOHV, its designated service providers, or third-party advertisers or their advertising servers may also place or recognize unique cookies on your computer or use other electronic tools in order to help display advertisements that you see on this Website or on other websites. Information about your visits to, and activity on, this Website and other websites, an IP address, the number of times you have viewed an advertisement, and other such usage information is used, alone or in combination with other information, to display on your device screen advertisements that may be of particular interest to you. We may use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising and product performance. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this Website, and to learn which banner ads bring users to this Website. The use and collection of your information by these third-party service providers, and third-party advertisers and their advertising servers is not covered by this Privacy Policy.
Service providers assist TOHV with advertisement display functions and related analytics for this Website. To opt out of or control Ad personalization based on Google’s data, please click here. To opt out of Facebook advertising on OTT devices, please click here.
Note that even if you exercise choice for targeted advertising, you will still receive online advertising.
Disclosure of Your Personal Information
TOHV may share your personal information with our affiliates (including affiliated websites under common ownership or control) and designated service providers, including for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. TOHV may share with other third parties information about our Website users, such as your use of this Website or other websites, and the services provided on this Website or other websites, but only on an unattributed and aggregate basis. TOHV may also share your personal information (excluding security photographs) with a sponsor or other third party (“Third-Party Provider”) that provides you with offers or promotions that may be of interest to you. You may instruct TOHV at any time not to share your personal information covered by this Privacy Policy with such Third-Party Providers by clicking here or, if you are TOHV Magazine subscriber, by clicking on the TOHV Magazine Opt-out form. Please note that (i) this opt-out process may take some time to complete, consistent with applicable law; and (ii) even after such opt-out process is completed, your personal information may continue to be shared with our affiliates (including affiliated websites under common ownership or control) and designated service providers.
If you participate in certain features of this Website (e.g., sharing news stories of interest), please note that any information you or others voluntarily disclose through use of these features, becomes available to the public and/or other users whom you have designated. If you choose to provide access to designated individuals, please be aware that any information you post will be visible to such individuals for their use. TOHV is not responsible for the information that you or others choose to disclose publicly on this Website, and neither TOHV’s nor others’ use of such information is subject to this Privacy Policy.
TOHV may also disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with any applicable law, rule, or regulation, or in response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal; (b) protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of TOHV or others; (c) monitor compliance with and enforce any terms of service on this Website; (d) provide our services and products (including allowing a purchaser of TOHV or a TOHV division to continue to serve you); (e) perform other activities related to such services and products, including billing and collection; (f) provide you with offers or promotions from TOHV; or (g) operate the systems that provide our services and products properly.
The collection, further use, and/or disclosure of your information by Third-Party Providers or by other third parties is not the responsibility of TOHV. Rather, such collection, use, and/or disclosure is governed by the third parties’ privacy policies.
Accuracy, Security, and Retention of Your Personal Information
Any personal information you provide to TOHV is kept on secure servers. TOHV uses security measures appropriate to the provision of the relevant product or service, such as reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures (a) to safeguard personal information against loss, theft, unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification; and (b) to ensure the integrity of the personal information. To help us protect your privacy, you should maintain the secrecy of the logon ID and password you may have set up in connection with your participation in this Website’s service. Personal information is retained for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which it is collected, including legitimate business reasons, and/or legal and regulatory requirements.
Rights with Respect to Your Personal Information
Depending on the jurisdiction, you may have the right to access, correct, delete, or restrict use of certain personal information covered by this Privacy Policy. Depending on the jurisdiction, you may also have the right to request that we refrain from processing personal information. Please bear in mind that if you exercise such rights this may affect our ability to provide our products and services. For inquiries about your personal information, please contact us by clicking here. While TOHV will make reasonable efforts to accommodate your request, we also reserve the right to impose certain restrictions and requirements on such requests, if allowed or required by applicable laws.
Please note that it may take some time to process your request, consistent with applicable law.
Links to Third-Party Websites
TOHV may provide links to third-party websites, including social networking websites. Since we do not control third-party sites and are not responsible for any information you may provide while on such sites, we encourage you to read the privacy policies on those websites before providing any of your information on such sites.
Questions Regarding This Privacy Policy
If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by clicking here. Please include “Privacy” in the Subject line of your inquiry. If you have complaints about TOHV’s processing of your personal information, you may have the right to contact the applicable supervisory authority.
Your California Privacy Rights
California’s “Shine the Light” law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about the businesses’ practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Alternately, such businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option to opt-out of such information-sharing. As discussed above, if you wish to opt-out of our sharing of your information with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes offline please click here, or for email please click here.
You may also make such a request by writing to us at:
TOHV reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions on this Web page. Such changes will be effective upon posting.
We've made updates to our Privacy Policy to support new EU data protection laws.
By continuing, you accept and agree to the terms.
Learn more about our Privacy Policy here.Ok
